today we're talking about side hustles
that you can do from bed
as you guys know we are in a time where
we are still
staying home most of the time and we
need some extra money with
everything that's going on in the world
the economy it's time for some extra
money
so today i'm going to share some side
hustles that you can do right from the
comfort of your home
i'm wearing a cozy sweater because it's
cold
even though i live in florida and what's
cold to me it's probably not cold to you
but
a little chilly in the house so we're
going to break down some side hustles
i do have a full playlist on different
side hustles i think i have like 10 15
videos on different side hustle
ideas so definitely check that out
because there's so many different ideas
way more that i'm going to share in this
video
so check them out also if you're new
welcome my name is kellyanne smith with
freedom in a budget and on this channel
i talk about saving money investing
growing your income
entrepreneurship so if that's something
that interests you definitely subscribe
to the channel and
stick around so jumping right in number
one is a
social media manager and this is
something that a lot of
influencers will hire someone that can
run their social media
and run their pinterest their facebook
their instagram
schedule posts and just make sure that
everything is flowing smoothly and that
they're able to
market their brand market their business
that they've created
and this can actually bring in quite a
great income
and it can range from cost per post
or it could be a set monthly fee or
there's different ways that people will
price it out
and this is something that is really
easy especially if you already
know social media well now sometimes you
do have to understand
marketing on the back end but that is
totally something that you can learn
as you go and really educate yourself
ahead of time there's courses that you
can take
youtube videos blog posts different
things to learn the importance of
marketing social media and the best ways
to do it the best ways to post the best
ways to write captions
all of that but it's something that you
can do from the comfort of your bed
if you're a creative person this is
gonna be right up your alley
number two is a graphic designer and
this is something that if you're
creative as well this is gonna be a
great
thing that you can do now this could be
making flyers for people this could be
making social media posts and graphics
and the little graphics that you see
with text and different things and
infographics this could be
editing photos this could be all
different types of
graphic media and different things that
you can do to help
other people help brands and you could
even offer this on places like fiverr
upwork where people will say hey i need
a graphic designer to create this image
for me this is my vision
please create this and it's something
that you can do right from the comfort
of your bed as well
if you're someone that has always done
side hustles and really want to take
it up a notch really make it into a
business i do have a full course called
dreamer to profitable that takes a
dream that you have that passion that
you have and to make it profitable and
to make it into something that you can
get a really great
income a side income and turn it into a
full-blown income so if you're wanting
to
start a business or start side hustling
and really take it to the next level
get into the nitty-gritty of how to
create systems how to
get confidence in pitching and how to
create different revenue streams
really dig into all of that i even have
a lawyer coming in for a legal guide
i have tons and tons of different
modules for it so
i do have a course down below in the
description box or dreamerprofitable.com
definitely check it out it's going to be
something that's going to help you
really take that to the next level next
is to search jobs online
that are remote nowadays with everything
that 2020 has happened
so many companies are moving to remote
employees and
that could be part-time remote full-time
remote but there are so many different
positions that you can just
simply search remote on monster.com
indeed different places like that
and really find awesome side jobs that
you can do from the comfort of your bed
from the comfort of your home
and it's something that's super easy
they set you up with all the equipment
you may need
pretty much you just need an internet
connection and you can get the job done
next is copywriting so this is something
that is really
a huge potential huge money maker and
this
is writing copy so this is writing email
copy or sales pages likes landing pages
for courses
or even captions or weekly newsletters
but
so many people like myself struggle with
writing i am totally more comfortable on
youtube than i am on my blog
and it's something that i struggle with
a lot when i have my course i actually
hired someone
to write my email funnel and my sales
page and i paid them fifteen hundred
dollars
now this probably didn't take very long
for them maybe a few hours and i made
fifteen hundred dollars for it
now that's after she had worked up her
portfolio a little bit worked up her
experience
but after a year or two you can really
charge a great
amount of money and make some really
really good money if you're good at
creative writing and really just being
able to
pitch a brand or pitch a company that's
something that is really going to be
helpful
and so important to so many brands and
they're willing to pay because i don't
want to be sitting there in front of a
blank computer screen
thinking what the heck am i going to
write no i'd rather just hire someone
and that way i can focus my efforts on
something else that's going to make me
more money
next is transcribing so people will hire
transcribers
to transcribe videos or podcasts or
trainings
different things that they need
transcriptions for just to even have a
personal record for
or to turn into a blog post or turn into
a different form of
media that they can use a different way
that they can publish a content and
reuse it
so transcription is such a great way
that you can if you're a fast typer and
good at typing
that you can use that as a side hustle
that you can do right from home
there's different transcription services
that you can look up and that you can
get paid
online and great great income of doing
it and this is a great one because you
can go at your own pace and you can do
it on your own time
if you found this video helpful please
take a second to like the video it
really helps with youtube algorithm
also subscribe and hit the bell so you
get notified every time that i upload
next is being a virtual assistant now
this is something that
kind of is some of the things that we've
talked about but all in one
so a lot of virtual assistants that i've
hired in the past what they do for me is
they will
help me brainstorm projects that i'm
working on they will help with my social
media they will
create pinterest graphics for me they'll
schedule pinterest
they'll write blog posts for me they
will do some of my email marketing
they're kind of like
the behind the scenes of my business all
the stuff that
yes i can do but it's kind of tedious
tasks that i don't really enjoy doing or
tasks that
i'm able to hire out so that i can focus
on
other things now i can't really hire out
someone to create my videos because i'm
the face of freedom in a budget
so i can hire out someone to do the back
end work and that way
it'll free up time for me to create more
videos for you virtual assistants can
range in cost
depending on their experience level as
well it's definitely something that you
work up your fees
typically when you're starting you don't
make too too much but then as you get
better more experienced more
testimonials you can increase your rates
next
is online surveys now online surveys
i'll be honest they don't make a ton
but if you're gonna be sitting there on
the couch or in bed or whatever it is
hey you might as well make a couple
extra bucks and i do have some links to
different online surveys down below
if you're already sitting on the couch
doing you know tv or whatever might as
well make some extra money brands will
hire to have these service creators so
that they can use this market research
to know how to better serve their
customers what people want
so it's a great way to make a couple
extra bucks trust me it's not much
but hey if you're in college might as
well do it or just sitting on the couch
might as well do it next is freelance
writing so freelance writing is very
similar to copywriting
but typically it's more blog posts or
writing scripts
or writing copy pages different things
like that and this is something that you
can do on places like fiverr or
upwork where you will set your price and
say hey
i will charge 50 for a blog post and i
will write
500 words for this blog post or if you
want to upgrade you can do
a thousand words 1500 words for this
price and
then you just give me the topic and then
they will write the blog post for you so
this is something that a lot a lot a lot
of vloggers use
is these ghostwriters where you may not
even know
but it's something that they can use to
then produce more content for their blog
and it's a really great way to to make
some extra money if you're good at
writing you can also put in there what
topics you're good at writing so it
doesn't have to be personal finance like
my brand
maybe it could be beauty maybe it could
be travel maybe it could be mom life
maybe it could be cooking maybe it could
be
fixing appliances around the house
there's so many different genres that
are in those topics and that people need
ghost writers for so freelancing is a
really really great way to make some
extra money let's keep the conversation
going if you want more side hustle ideas
check out this playlist here and if you
want to know how much i make on youtube
behind the scenes
check out this video here
[Music]